Finding aid for News and Information Services (University of Michigan) records, 1900-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library
- Topical files
  - 1988
    - Psychology Department of (LSA) (Box 117)
    - Public Health, School of (Box 117)
    - Public Policy Studies, Institute of (Box 118)
    - Public Safety and Security, 2 folders (Box 118)
    - Recreational Sports (Box 118)
    - Regents, 2 folders (Box 118)
    - Registrar, Office of the (Box 118)
    - Research Development and Administration, Division of (Box 118)
    - Research, Division of (Business Administration) (Box 118)
    - Research, Office of the Vice-President for (Box 118)
    - Research Seminar in Quantitative Economics (Box 118)
    - Residential College (Box 118)
    - Romance Languages and Literatures (Box 118)
    - ROTC (General) (Box 118)
    - Russel, Henry, Lecture Awards (Box 118)
    - Russian and East European Studies, Center for (Box 118)
    - Science and Technology, Institute of (Box 118)
    - Senate Assembly (Box 118)
    - Slavic Languages and Literatures (Box 118)
    - Social Research, Institute for, 2 folders (Box 118)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 118)
    - Sociology, Department of (Box 118)
    - South and Southeast Asian Studies, Center for (Box 118)
    - Student Activities (folder 1 of 5) (Box 118)
    - Student Activities (folders 2-5) (Box 119)
    - Student Affairs, Office of the Vice President (Box 119)
    - Student Organizations, Office of, 5 folders (Box 119)
      (See also 1989 accession)
    - Student Publications (Box 119)
    - Survey Research Center (Box 119)
    - Theater and Drama Department (Box 119)
    - Transportation Research Institute (Box 119)
    - University Health Service (Box 119)
    - University Housing (Box 119)
    - University Musical Society (Box 119)
    - University of Michigan (General) (Box 119)
    - University Relations (Box 119)
    - Wallenberg, Raoul, Lecture (Box 119)
    - Western European Studies, Center for (Box 119)
    - Women (General)Women's Studies Program (Box 119)
    - WUOM/WVGR/WFUM-FM (radio stations) (Box 119)
  - 1989
    - Academic Affairs (Box 121)
    - Academic Affairs, Office of Vice President and Provost for (Box 121)
    - Admissions, Office of Undergraduate (Box 121)
    - Aerospace Engineering, Department of (Box 121)
    - Affirmative Action Office (Box 121)
    - Afro-American / African Studies, Center for (Box 121)
    - Alumni Association (Box 121)
    - Anthropology, Department of (Box 121)
    - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of (Box 121)
    - Art, School of (Box 121)
    - Asian Studies (Box 121)
    - Astronomy, Department of (LSA) (Box 121)
    - Atmospheric and Oceanic Science, Department of (Box 121)
    - Biological Station (Box 121)
    - Biology, Department of (Box 121)
    - Biophysics Research Division (Box 121)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 121)
    - Budget (Box 121)
    - Buildings (Box 121)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 121)
    - Career Planning and Placement (Box 121)
    - Chemical Engineering, Department of (Box 121)
    - Chemistry, Department of (Box 121)
    - Chinese Studies, Center for (Box 121)
    - Civil and Environmental Engineering, Dept. of (Box 121)
    - Classical Studies, Department of, LSA (Box 121)
    - Clements Library, William L. (Box 121)
    - Commencement (Box 121)
    - Committees (University-wide) (Box 121)
    - Communication, Department of (Box 121)
    - Comprehensive Studies Program / Opportunity Program (Box 121)
    - Consumer Attitudes, Survey of (Box 121)
    - Dearborn Campus
      - 1988 (Box 121)
      - 1989 (Box 121)
    - Dentistry, School of (Box 121)
    - Development and Communication, Vice Pres. for (Box 121)
    - Economic Development, Center for Research on (Box 121)
    - Economic Development (State and Ann Arbor) (Box 121)
    - Economics, Department of (Box 121)
    - Education of Women, Center for the (CEW) (Box 122)
    - Education, School of (Box 122)
    - Educom (Box 122)
    - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, Department of, 2 folders (Box 122)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 122)
    - English, Department of (LSA) (Box 122)
    - English Composition Board (Box 122)
    - Enrollment (Box 122)
    - Environmental and Industrial Health, Institute of (Box 122)
    - Ethics and Religion, Office for (Box 122)
    - Extension Service (Box 122)
    - Faculty (Box 122)
    - Fees (Box 122)
    - Film and Video Studies, Program in (Box 122)
    - Financial, also Financial Officer, Vice President and Chief (Box 122)
    - Financial Aid, Office of Student (Box 122)
    - Flint Campus (Box 122)
    - Ford Presidential Library (Box 122)
    - General Counsel (Box 122)
    - Geological Sciences, Department of (Box 122)
    - Germanic Languages and Literature, Dept. of (Box 122)
    - Gerontology, Institute of (Box 122)
    - Government Relations, Vice President for (Box 122)
    - Graduate Studies, Horace H. Rackham School of (Box 122)
    - Great Lakes and Marine Waters Center (Box 122)
    - Great Lakes Research Division (LSA Natural Resources) (Box 122)
    - History, Department of (LSA) (Box 122)
    - History of Art, Department of (Box 122)
    - Hometown Stories (Box 122)
    - Honorary Degrees (Box 122)
    - Honors
      - Faculty (Box 122)
      - Student (Box 122)
    - Hopwood Awards (Box 122)
    - Human Adjustment, Institute for (Box 122)
    - Human Growth and Development, Center for (Box 122)
    - Humanities, Institute for the (Box 122)
    - Industrial Development Division (IDD) (Box 122)
    - Industrial and Operations Engineering, Dept. of (Box 122)
    - Information and Library Studies, School of (Box 122)
    - Information Technology, Vice Provost for (Box 122)
    - Intercollegiate Athletics, 1 folder (Box 122)
    - Intercollegiate Athletics, 4 folders (Box 123)
    - International Center (Box 123)
    - Inter-University Consortium for Political and Social Research (Box 123)
    - Japanese Studies, Center for (Box 123)
    - Judaic Studies Program (Box 123)
    - Kellogg Foundation Institute, W.K. (Dentistry) (Box 123)
    - Kelsey Museum (Box 123)
    - Kinesiology, Physical Education, Division of (Box 123)
    - Labor and Industrial Relations, Institute of (ILIR) (Box 123)
    - Law School (Box 123)
    - Learning and Teaching, Center for Research on (Box 123)
    - Libraries (Box 123)
    - Linguistics, Program in (Box 123)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of (Box 123)
    - Mathematics, Department of (Box 123)
    - Medical School (Box 123)
    - Michigan Historical Collections (Includes Bentley Library) (Box 123)
    - Michigan League (Box 123)
    - Michigan Media Resource Center (Box 123)
    - Michigan Quarterly Review (Box 123)
    - Michigan Sea Grant College Program (Engineering) (Box 123)
    - Michigan Union (Box 123)
    - Minority Affairs, Vice-Provost for, 4 folders
      - Folders 1-2 (Box 123)
      - Folders 3-4 (Box 124)
    - Museum of Art (Box 124)
    - Music, School of (Box 124)
    - Natural Resources, School of (Box 124)
    - Natural Science Museums (Box 124)
    - Near Eastern and North African Studies, Center for (Box 124)
    - News and Information Services (Box 124)
    - Nuclear Engineering, Department of (Box 124)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 124)
    - Occupational Safety and Environmental Health (Box 124)
    - Personnel (Box 124)
    - Pharmacy, College of (Box 124)
    - Philosophy, Department of (Box 124)
    - Physics, Department of (LSA) (Box 124)
    - Plant Extension; Plant Operations (Box 124)
    - Political Science, Department of (Box 124)
    - Political Studies, Center for (ISR) (Box 124)
    - Population Planning, Center for (Public Health) (Box 124)
    - Population Studies Center (LSA) (Box 124)
    - President, Office of the (Box 124)
    - Presidents of National Associations (Box 124)
    - Press Releases, Other Colleges and Universities (Box 124)
    - Psychology Department of (LSA) (Box 124)
    - Public Health, School of (Box 124)
    - Public Policy Studies, Institute of (Box 124)
    - Public Safety and Security, Department of (Box 124)
    - Recreational Sports (Box 124)
    - Regents (Box 124)
    - Registrar, Office of the (Box 124)
    - Research Development and Administration (Box 124)
    - Research, Division of (Business Administration) (Box 124)
    - Research, Office of the Vice President for (Box 124)
    - Research Seminar in Quantitative Economics (Box 125)
    - Reserve Officers Training Corps (ROTC) (Box 125)
    - Residential College (Box 125)
    - Romance Languages and Literatures, Dept. of (Box 125)
    - Russel Lectures and Awards, Henry (Box 125)
    - Russian and East European Studies, Center for (Box 125)
    - Science and Technology, Institute of (IST) (Box 125)
    - Senate Assembly (Box 125)
    - Slavic Languages and Literatures, Department of (Box 125)
    - Social Research, Institute for (ISR) (Box 125)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 125)
    - Sociology, Department of (LSA) (Box 125)
    - South and Southeast Asian Studies, Center for (Box 125)
    - Student Activities, 3 folders (Box 125)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President for (Box 125)
    - Student Organizations, 1988-1989; 7 folders (Box 125)
    - Student Organizations, 1988-1989; 4 folders (Box 126)
    - Student Publications, Board for (Box 126)
    - Theater and Drama Department of (Music) (Box 126)
    - Transportation Research Institute, University of Michigan (UMTRI) (Box 126)
    - University Health Service (Box 126)
    - University Housing (Box 126)
    - University Musical Society (Box 126)
    - University of Michigan (General) (Box 126)
    - University of Michigan Hospitals
      - 1988, 2 folders (Box 126)
      - 1989, 4 folders (Box 126)
    - University of Michigan Press (Box 127)
    - University Relations (Box 127)
    - US-Japan Auto Conference (Box 127)
    - Western European Studies, Center for (Box 127)
    - Women (General) (Box 127)
    - Women's Studies Program (Box 127)
    - WUOM/WVGR/WFUM-FM (radio stations), 2 folders (Box 127)
  - 1990
    - Academic Affairs, Office of Vice President and Provost for (Box 127)
    - Academic and Multicultural Affairs, Vice Provost for (Box 127)
    - Admissions Office (Box 127)
    - Aerospace Engineering, Department of (Box 127)
    - Affirmative Action Office (Box 127)
    - Afro-American/African Studies (Box 127)
    - Alumni Association (Box 127)
    - Anthropology, Department of (Box 127)
    - Art, School of (Box 127)
    - Asian Languages and Cultures (formerly Far Eastern Languages and Literatures) (Box 127)
    - Astronomy, Department of (LSA) (Box 127)
    - Atmospheric and Oceanic Science (Box 127)
    - Biological Station (Box 127)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 127)
    - Budget (Box 127)
    - Buildings (Box 127)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 127)
    - Career Planning and Placement (Box 127)
    - Chemical Engineering (Box 127)
    - Chemistry (Box 127)
    - Chinese Studies, Center for (Box 127)
    - Civil and Environmental Engineering (Box 127)
    - Classical Studies (Box 127)
    - Clements Library, William L. (Box 127)
    - Commencement (Box 127)
    - Commission for Women (Box 127)
    - Committees (University-wide) (Box 127)
    - Communication, Department of (Box 127)
    - Comprehensive Studies Program/Opportunity Program (Box 127)
    - Computing Center (Box 127)
    - Consumer Attitudes, Survey of (Box 127)
    - Continuing Legal Education (Box 127)
    - Dentistry, School of (Box 127)
    - Development and Communication Office (Box 127)
    - Economic Development, Center for Research on (Box 127)
    - Economic Development (State and Ann Arbor) (Box 127)
    - Economics, Department of (Box 127)
    - Education of Women, Center for the (CEW) (Box 128)
    - Education, School of (Box 128)
    - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science (Box 128)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 128)
    - English, Department of (LSA) (Box 128)
    - English Composition Board (Box 128)
    - English Language Institute (Box 128)
    - Enrollment (Box 128)
    - Ethics and Religion, Office for (Box 128)
    - Extension Office (Box 128)
    - Faculty (Box 128)
    - Fees (Box 128)
    - Financial (Box 128)
    - Financial Aid, Student, Office of (Box 128)
    - Flint Campus (Box 128)
    - General Counsel (Box 128)
    - Geography (Box 128)
    - Geological Sciences, Department of (Box 128)
    - Germanic Languages and Literature (Box 128)
    - Gerontology, Institute of (Box 128)
    - Government Relations (Box 128)
    - Graduate Studies, Horace H. Rackham School of (Box 128)
    - History, Department of (LSA) (Box 128)
    - History of Art, Department of (Box 128)
    - Hometown Stories (Box 128)
    - Honorary Degrees (Box 128)
    - Honors
      - Faculty (Box 128)
      - Student (Box 128)
    - Hopwood Awards (Box 128)
    - Human Growth and Development, Center for (Box 128)
    - Humanities, Institute for the (Box 128)
    - Industrial Development Division (Box 128)
    - Industrial and Operations Engineering (Box 128)
    - Information and Library Studies, School of (Box 128)
    - Information Technology, Office of the Vice Provost (Box 128)
    - Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 128)
    - International Center (Box 128)
    - Inter-University Consortium for Political and Social Research (Box 128)
    - Japanese Studies, Center for (Box 128)
    - Judaic Studies Program (Box 128)
    - Kellogg Foundation Institute, WK. (Box 128)
    - Kelsey, Museum of Ancient and Medieval Archaeology (Box 128)
    - Kinesiology (Box 128)
    - Labor and Industrial Relations, Institute of (ILIR) (Box 128)
    - Law School (Box 128)
    - Learning and Teaching, Center for Research on (Box 128)
    - Libraries (Box 128)
    - Linguistics (Box 128)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of (Box 128)
    - Materials Science and Engineering, Department of (Box 128)
    - Mathematics, Department of (Box 128)
    - Mechanical Engineering and Applied Mechanics (Box 128)
    - Medical Affairs, Vice-Provost for (Box 128)
    - Medical Center (Box 128)
    - Michigan Law Review (Box 128)
    - Michigan League (Box 128)
    - Michigan Media Resource Center (Box 128)
    - Michigan Quarterly Review (Box 128)
    - Michigan Sea Grant College Program (Box 129)
    - Michigan Union (Box 129)
    - Middle Eastern and North African Studies Center (Box 129)
    - Minority Affairs, Vice-Provost for (Box 129)
    - Minority Groups (Box 129)
    - Museum of Art (Box 129)
    - Music, School of (Box 129)
    - Natural Resources, School of (Box 129)
    - Natural Science Museums (Box 129)
    - Near Eastern and N. African Studies, Center for (Box 129)
    - News and Information Services (Box 129)
    - Nuclear Engineering, Department of (Box 129)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 129)
    - Occupational Safety and Environmental Health (Box 129)
    - Personnel (Box 129)
    - Pharmacy, College of (Box 129)
    - Philosophy, Department of (Box 129)
    - Physics, Department of (Box 129)
    - Plant Extension--Plant Operations (Box 129)
    - Political Science, Department of (Box 129)
    - Population Studies Center (Box 129)
    - President, Office of (Box 129)
    - Psychology Department of (LSA) (Box 129)
    - Public Health, School of (Box 129)
    - Public Policy Studies, Institute of (Box 129)
    - Public Safety and Security (Box 129)
    - Recreational Sports (Box 129)
    - Registrar, Office of the (Box 129)
    - Research Development and Administration, Division of (Box 129)
    - Research, Office of the Vice President for (Box 129)
    - Research Seminar in Quantitative Economics (Box 129)
    - Residential College (Box 129)
    - Romance Languages and Literatures (Box 129)
    - ROTC (General) (Box 129)
    - Russel, Henry, Lecture Awards (Box 129)
    - Russian and East European Studies, Center for (Box 129)
    - Science and Technology, Institute of (Box 129)
    - Senate Assembly (Box 130)
    - Slavic Languages and Literatures (Box 130)
    - Social Research, Institute for (Box 130)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 130)
    - Sociology, Department of (Box 130)
    - Solar Car (Sunrunner) (Box 130)
    - South and Southeast Asian Studies, Center for (Box 130)
    - Student Activities, 3 folders (Box 130)
    - Student Affairs, Office of the Vice President for (Box 130)
    - Student Organizations (Box 130)
    - Student Organizations, Office of, 2 folders (Box 130)
    - Student Publications (Box 130)
    - Survey Research Center (Box 131)
    - University Health Service (Box 131)
    - University of Michigan Hospital (2) (Box 131)
    - University Housing (Box 131)
    - University Musical Society (Box 131)
    - University of Michigan (General) (Box 131)
    - University of Michigan Press (Box 131)
    - University Relations, Vice President for (Box 131)
    - Western European Studies, Center for (Box 131)
    - Women (General) (Box 131)
    - Women's Studies Program (Box 131)
    - WUOM/WVGR/WFUM-FM (radio stations) (Box 131)
  - 1991
    - Academic Affairs, Office of Vice President and Provost for (Box 131)
    - Academic and Multicultural Affairs, Vice Provost for (Box 131)
    - Admissions Office (Box 131)
    - Aerospace Engineering, Department of (Box 131)
    - Affirmative Action Office (Box 131)
    - Afro-American/African Studies (Box 131)
    - Alumni Association (Box 131)
    - Anthropology, Department of (Box 131)
    - Architecture and Urban Planning (Box 131)
    - Art, School of (Box 131)
    - Astronomy, Department of (LSA) (Box 131)
    - Atmospheric and Oceanic Science (Box 131)
    - Biological Station (Box 131)
    - Biology, Department of (Box 131)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 131)
    - Budget (Box 131)
    - Buildings (Box 132)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 132)
    - Career Planning and Placement (Box 132)
    - Chemical Engineering (Box 132)
    - Chemistry (Box 132)
    - Chinese Studies, Center for (Box 132)
    - Civil and Environmental Engineering (Box 132)
    - Classical Studies (Box 132)
    - Clements Library, William L. (Box 132)
    - Commencement (Box 132)
    - Committees (University-wide) (Box 132)
    - Communication, Department of (Box 132)
    - Community Affairs (Box 132)
    - Comprehensive Studies Program/Opportunity Program (Box 132)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 132)
    - Dentistry, School of (Box 132)
    - Development and Communication Office (Box 132)
    - Economic Development, Center for Research on (Box 132)
    - Economic development (State and Ann Arbor) (Box 132)
    - Economics, Department of (Box 132)
    - Education of Women, Center for the (Box 132)
    - Education, School of (Box 132)
    - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science (Box 132)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 132)
    - English, Department of (LSA) (Box 132)
    - Enrollment (Box 132)
    - Environmental and Industrial Health, Institute of (Box 132)
    - Ethics and Religion, Office for (Box 132)
    - Extension Office (Box 132)
    - Faculty (Box 132)
    - Fees (Box 132)
    - Film and Video (Box 132)
    - Financial Aid, Student, Office of (Box 132)
    - Financial Officer (Box 132)
    - Ford Presidential Library (Box 132)
    - General Counsel (Box 132)
    - Geography (Box 132)
    - Geological Sciences, Department of (Box 132)
    - Germanic Languages and Literature (Box 132)
    - Gerontology, Institute of (Box 132)
    - Government Relations (Box 132)
    - Graduate Studies, Horace H. Rackham School of (Box 132)
    - Great Lakes and Marine Water Center (Box 132)
    - Great Lakes Research Division (Box 132)
    - History, Department of (LSA) (Box 132)
    - History of Art, Department of (Box 132)
    - Hometown Stories (Box 132)
    - Honorary Degrees (Box 132)
    - Honors
      - Faculty (Box 132)
      - Student (Box 132)
    - Honors Council (Box 132)
    - Hopwood Awards (Box 132)
    - Human Adjustment, Institute for (Box 132)
    - Human Growth and Development, Center for (Box 132)
    - Humanities, Institute for the (Box 132)
    - Industrial and Operations Engineering (Box 132)
    - Information and Library Studies, School of (Box 132)
    - Information Technology, Office of the Vice Provost (Box 132)
    - Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 133)
    - International Center (Box 133)
    - Japanese Studies, Center for (Box 133)
    - Judaic Studies Program (Box 133)
    - Kelsey Museum (Box 133)
    - Kinesiology (Box 133)
    - Kresge Hearing Research Institute (Box 133)
    - Labor and Industrial Relations, Institute of (ILIR) (Box 133)
    - Law School (Box 133)
    - Learning and Teaching, Center for Research on (Box 133)
    - Libraries (Box 133)
    - Linguistics (Box 133)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of (Box 133)
    - Mathematics, Department of (Box 133)
    - Mechanical Engineering and Applied Mechanics (Box 133)
    - Medical Affairs, Vice Provost for (Box 133)
    - Medical School (Box 133)
    - Mental Health Research Institute (Box 133)
    - Michigan Historical Collections (Bentley Historical Library) (Box 133)
    - Michigan League (Box 133)
    - Michigan Quarterly Review (Box 133)
    - Michigan Sea Grant College Program (Box 133)
    - Michigan Union (Box 133)
    - Middle Eastern and North African Studies Center (Box 133)
    - Museum of Art (Box 133)
    - Music, School of (Box 133)
    - Natural Resources, School of (Box 133)
    - Natural Science Museums (Box 133)
    - Near Eastern and North African Studies, Center (Box 133)
    - News and Information Services (Box 133)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 133)
    - Occupational Safety and Environmental Health (Box 133)
    - Personnel (Box 133)
    - Pharmacy, College of (Box 133)
    - Phoenix Project (Box 133)
    - Philosophy, Department of (Box 133)
    - Physics, Department of (Box 133)
    - Plant Extension, Plant Operations (Box 133)
    - Political Science, Department of (Box 133)
    - Political Studies, Center for (Box 133)
    - Population Planning Center (Box 133)
    - Population Studies Center (Box 133)
    - President, Office of (Box 133)
    - Psychology Department of (LSA) (Box 133)
    - Public Health, School of (Box 133)
    - Public Policy Studies, Institute of (Box 133)
    - Public Safety and Security (Box 133)
    - Racism (Box 134)
    - Recreational Sports (Box 134)
    - Regents (Box 134)
    - Registrar, Office of the (Box 134)
    - Research Development and Administration, Division of (Box 134)
    - Research, Division of (Business Administration) (Box 134)
    - Research, Office of the Vice President for (Box 134)
    - Research Seminar in Quantitative Economics (Box 134)
    - Residential College (Box 134)
    - Romance Languages and Literatures (Box 134)
    - ROTC (General) (Box 134)
    - Russel, Henry, Lecture Awards (Box 134)
    - Russian and East European Studies, Center for (Box 134)
    - Science and Technology, Institute of (Box 134)
    - Senate Assembly (Box 134)
    - Slavic Languages and Literatures (Box 134)
    - Social Research, Institute for (Box 134)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 134)
    - Sociology, Department of (Box 134)
    - South and Southeast Asian Studies, Center for (Box 134)
    - Student Activities, 2 folders (Box 134)
    - Student Affairs, Office of the Vice President for (Box 134)
    - Student Organizations, 3 folders (Box 134)
    - Student Publications (Box 135)
    - Survey Research Center (Box 135)
    - Transportation Research Institute (Box 135)
    - University Health Service (Box 135)
    - University Housing (Box 135)
    - University Musical Society (Box 135)
    - University of Michigan (General) (Box 135)
    - University of Michigan Press (Box 135)
    - University Relations (Box 135)
    - Women (General) (Box 135)
    - Women's Studies Program (Box 135)
    - WUOM/WVGR/WFUM-FM (radio stations) (Box 135)
  - 1992
    - Academic Affairs, Vice Provost and Vice President for (Box 135)